♪The world keeps changing♪
♪A thousand years pass
in the blink of an eye♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder♪
♪We stand above the world♪
♪Our identities switch♪
♪The world turns upside down♪
♪Watch me♪
♪Stir up a storm♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our blood is boiling♪
♪The genius emperor plots
with brilliant strategy♪
♪The slacker general
is unmatched in battle♪
♪The business world is in turmoil♪
♪The court is rife with intrigue♪
♪We will conquer the world♪
♪There's no escape for the traitors♪
=No Way! My Bro is the Emperor=
=Episode 19=
This is...
The Western Yi totem?
Hu Wenyuan and I
are both from the Western Yi.
I don't know
where the money ended up,
but
I'm sure the Western Yi are involved.
Looks like the Western Yi
seeks this marriage alliance
for another purpose.
Do you think I did all this
just to make money?
Xiao Ce,
you're still too naive.
Did it never occur to you
what we needed
all that money for?
Could it be
there's someone
behind Hu Wenyuan?
A nation's stability
rests upon the rule of law.
The realm prospers
through loyal ministers.
Gu Bei
tracked down the traffickers
with courage and resolve,
putting an end to the chaos
and bringing peace to the people.
It greatly pleases me.
Therefore, I hereby promote him in rank
to honor his service.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I invited
the Princess Royal today
so
we could all celebrate
the eradication of Fushou Cream
from Jing.
Of course,
I'd also like to ask Aunt
to offer prayers
for those who lost their lives
because of Fushou Cream.
Your Majesty is most compassionate.
I will do my utmost
to pray for all living beings.
Your Majesty,
the Western Yi delegation
will arrive in the capital soon.
Though Your Majesty
has no intention of a marriage alliance,
Jing is the leading empire,
we should still receive them
with due courtesy to display our grace.
Official Li makes a good point.
Then let
- Official Gu Bei handle the reception.
- I...
Though Official Gu
is loyal and brave,
he's never
dealt with the Western Yi before.
In the late Emperor's reign,
I accompanied him
on a diplomatic mission to the Western Yi
and learned something of their customs.
Why don't
I accompany Official Gu
to receive them?
Very well.
Thank you, Aunt.
(Why is the Princess Royal)
(suddenly become so concerned)
(with court affairs?)
(Changle Gate)
Quite the grand airs.
We've been waiting over two hours.
Official Gu,
please be patient.
The Western Yi people
have never been punctual.
Your Highness, why not head into the city
and get some rest?
Once they arrive,
I'll come
fetch you.
We agreed to welcome them together.
How could I leave you
here alone?
I'm Gu Bei,
Commander of the Imperial Guards,
sent by His Majesty to receive
the Western Yi delegation.
(Jiaye, Western Yi Envoy)
You've had a long journey.
Please proceed to the relay station.
I hear
Jing is rich in treasures.
Does the relay station
have fine wine and beautiful women?
Dismount.
Your Excellency,
it's the law in Jing.
Ridiculous.
In Western Yi,
we ride our horses
right into the royal palace.
Why can't we
ride through your city gate?
I'll say it again.
Dismount and enter on foot.
The Western Yi certainly are arrogant.
When the late Emperor reigned,
he seized eighteen prefectures
from Western Yi in battle.
Your king came
bearing a sheep to surrender.
Have you forgotten?
How dare you insult our king!
His Majesty has shown restraint
and spared you war.
Yet you dare behave so insolently?
Gu Bei.
Yes, Your Highness.
Listen carefully.
If they dismount
and enter the city peacefully,
they will be pardoned.
But if they insist
on defying Jing's authority,
kill them.
As you command,
Your servant obeys.
Gu Bei, after you've escorted them
to the relay station,
come to my residence.
I have something to ask you.
Your Highness.
Not a bad place.
(Huaitan Records)
Erotic paintings?
Wasn't she supposed to be devoted
to Buddhist practice?
Your Highness,
I've escorted the Western Yi envoys
to the relay station.
May I ask
why you summoned me?
Actually,
it's nothing.
I simply
want to make you
my male consort.
What's with that look?
Compose yourself.
The truth is,
I'm already in love.
With three women.
One of them is Xiao Ling.
How could I
marry her aunt?
I'm taking you in,
not the other way around.
As for your looks,
they're nothing special.
Among all my male consorts,
you wouldn't even make the top ten.
Weren't you living in a temple,
devoting yourself to Buddhism?
So why
have you given that up?
Because
I find you interesting.
What future
does an Imperial Guard commander have?
Stay with me,
and you'll enjoy a life of luxury.
You're His Majesty's aunt,
and he's my friend.
Wouldn't that
be inappropriate?
Men can have many wives and concubines,
and marry young women.
Why can't I take a younger man?
You certainly can.
It's just
I still have
something to do today.
Perhaps another time.
I didn't bring you here
to let you walk away.
Today,
you'll serve me.
Move.
What are you doing?
Please me,
and I
will reward you well.
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our spirit soars to the skies♪
♪The brainy emperor plots the strategy♪
♪The slacker general leads the charge♪
♪Swords clash and warhorses thunder♪
♪Let the history judge our deeds♪
♪Our brotherhood is priceless♪
♪Peace across the land, carefree at last♪
♪Funny moments never stop♪
♪Silly blunders never cease♪
♪Yet through every up and down♪
♪We create miracles♪
♪From naive youths♪
♪To legendary heroes♪
♪This journey♪
♪Is one we'll be proud of♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend of our own♪